quiz_data = [
    {
        "question": "Question 1: What is the largest planet in our solar system?",
        "choices": ["Jupiter", "Saturn", "Mars", "Earth"],
        "answer": "Jupiter"
    },
    {
        "question": "Question 2: What is the chemical symbol for gold?",
        "choices": ["Go", "Au", "Ag", "Gd"],
        "answer": "Au"
    },
    {
        "question": "Question 3: Which country is known as the 'Land of the Rising Sun'?",
        "choices": ["China", "Japan", "South Korea", "Thailand"],
        "answer": "Japan"
    },
    {	
        "question": "Question 4: Which is the largest ocean on Earth?",	
        "choices": ["Atlantic Ocean", "Pacific Ocean", "Arctic Ocean", "Indian Ocean"],
        "answer": "Pacific Ocean"
    },
    {	
        "question": "Question 5: What is the number of periods in the Periodic Table?",	
        "choices": ["6", "7", "8", "9"],
        "answer": "7"
    },
    {	
        "question": "Question 6: What is the longest river on Earth?",
        "choices": ["Amazon River", "Nile River", "Yamuna River", "Bhramaputra River"],
        "answer": "Nile River"
    },
    {	
        "question": "Question 7: What is the currency of Norway?",	
        "choices": ["Ruble", "Dollar", "Euro", "Krone"],	
        "answer": "Krone"
    },
    {	
        "question": "Question 8: When did India get independnce?",
        "choices": ["26th January,1950", "15th August,1947", "15th January,1947", "26th August,1950"],	
        "answer": "15th August,1947"
    },
    {	
        "question": "Question 9: Who is known as the 'Father of the Indian Constitution?",
        "choices": ["Dr. B R Ambedkar", "Rajendra Prasad", "Dadabhai Naoroji", "Rabindranath Tagore"],	
        "answer": "Dr. B R Ambedkar"
    },
    {	
        "question": "Question 10: Who is the author of the famous book series 'Harry Potter'?",
        "choices": ["Agatha Christie", "Stephen King", "Ernest Hemingway", "J K Rowling"],	
        "answer": "J K Rowling"
    }
]